我们以前居然没试过这样
I can't believe we've never done this before!
真舒服  莫妮卡好舒服
It's sooo good! So good for Monica!
时间到  该我了
Oh! Look at that, time's up! My turn!
已经半小时了吗
That was a half an hour?
计时器是你的
It's your timer.
我不想自夸
Y'know, I don't like to brag about it,
但我最会按摩了
but I give the best massages!
好吧  那就给我好好按按吧
All right, then massage me up right nice!
很舒服吧
It's so good, isn't it?
舒服到我觉得我无福消受
It's so good I don't know what I've done to deserve it!
跟酸痛肌肉说再见吧
Say good-bye to sore muscles!
再见了肌肉
Good-bye muscles!!
她的按摩技术烂到不行
I'm telling you, she gives the worst massages ever!!
她简直就像在严刑逼供
Okay, it was like she was torturing me for information.
我很想招  又不知道她要什么情报
And I wanted to give it up I just-I didn't know what it was!
钱德勒  如果真的很痛
Chandler, if it really hurts that bad
你就应该告诉她
you should just tell her.
我这辈子第一次这么认真地投入感情
Look, for the first time in my life I'm in a real relationship.
我可不想因为说实话  搞砸这段关系
Okay, I'm not gonna screw that up by y'know, telling the truth.
老兄  小心  你差点踩扁我的帽子
Whoa, dude, look out! You almost crushed my hat!
对不起
Sorry.
兔子呢  变没了吗
And the bunny got away.
你现在该解释一下这顶帽子
This would be the place where you explain the hat.
现在有出新戏
Oh! Yeah, look there's this play all right?
我要争取的角色
And I'm up for the part of this
是个温文尔雅的人
real cool like suave international guy.
很爱赶时髦
A real clothes horse.
所以我想去试镜的人
So I figure that everyone at the audition
一定都会穿得很时尚
is gonna be wearing this kinda y'know, ultra-hip,
很高档次
high fashion stuff.
你要把他们都变没吗
And you're gonna make them all disappear.
有什么比这顶帽子更有品位的
Yeah, like you could find something as sophisticated as this.
有了
Done.
乔伊  如果你想帅一点
Joey, if you wanna look good,
干嘛不到我们店里来  我帮你打扮
why don't you just come down to the store? I'll help you out.
太好了  谢谢  瑞秋
Great! Thanks, Rach!
-不客气  拜托  快拿掉  -好的
- Sure! God, please take those off! - All right.
菲比  今天好吗
Hey Pheebs, how's it going?
一般般
Hey! Umm, well, only okay
因为我刚去过医院
because I just got back from, from the hospital.
-没事吧  -你还好吗
- Is everything okay? - Are you all right?
我很好
Oh yeah, no-no-no. I'm fine. I'm okay,
但是我外婆死了
but umm, my Grandma sorta died.
菲比  别难过
Pheebs! Sorry!
没关系  她这一生过得很精彩
It's okay, I mean she had a really incredible life.
我也不是永远见不到她了
And it's not like I'm never gonna see her again,
她会来找我的
y'know she's gonna visit.
也许她现在就在这里
Well maybe, maybe she's with us right now?
对  她升天头一天
Yeah, her first day on a new spiritual plane
没准会逛逛咖啡馆
and she's gonna come to the coffeehouse!
外面车上有两个人在做爱
Guys! Guys! I just saw two people having sex in a car right outside.
菲比的外婆刚过世了
Uhh, Pheebs' Grandmother just died.
天哪  对不起
Ohh my God, I'm so sorry.
没事  其实这样还蛮酷的
It's okay. Actually y'know what, it's kinda cool.
就像一个生命结束  另一个生命开始了
'Cause it's like y'know, one life ends and another begins.
他们的做法很难制造生命
Not the way they're doing it.
怎么回事  她是怎么过世的
What, what happened? How did she die?
我们在超市
Well umm, okay we were in the market
她弯腰去拿酸奶
and she bent down to get some yogurt
就再也没起来了
and she just never came back up again.
菲比  真令人遗憾
Pheebs, I'm so sorry.
其实蛮甜蜜的  她的遗言是
It was really sweet. The last thing she said to me was;
亲爱的  你去拿鸡蛋
"Okay dear, you go get the eggs
我去拿酸奶  我们在收银台见
and I'm gonna get the yogurt and we'll meet at the checkout counter."
知道吗  我们绝对会在人生的收银台见
And y'know what? We will meet at the checkout counter.
乔伊  试镜后这身行头是要还的
Okay now Joey, y'know that since you're returning all of this stuff
所以你得穿内裤
right after the audition you're gonna have to wear underwear?
好  那你还得拿内裤给我
All right, then you'd better show me some of that too then.
还少了点什么
Okay, it's missing something.
我知道了
Ooh, I know! Umm, okay.
搞错没  手提包
Really? A purse?
这可不是手提包  这是挎包
It's not a purse! It's a shoulder bag.
看起来就是女式手提包
It looks like a women's purse.
不  乔伊
No Joey, look.
春季购物目录上的男模都在背
Trust me, all the men are carrying them in the spring catalog.
你看  男人  背包包
Look.  See look, men, carrying the bag.
你看  女人  背包包
See look, women, carrying the bag.
没想到我一个大男人背女用包居然这么帅
But it is odd how a women's purse looks good on me, a man.
没错  中性(音同"你需要性爱")
Exactly! Unisex!
你或许需要  我几天前刚做过
Maybe you need sex. I had sex a couple days ago.
不是  乔伊  男女通用(音同"你和我做爱")
No! No Joey! U-N-I-sex.
我绝对不会拒绝
Well, I ain't gonna say no to that.
哪位
Who is it?
菲比
It's Phoebe.
太好了
Oh great!
原来是你
Oh, you.
有什么事
Umm, what's up?
有个坏消息  我可以进去吗
Umm, well I sorta have some bad news, can I come in?
还是不要好了
Umm, yeah-no thanks.
外婆今天去世了
Grandma died.
她不是五年前就死了吗
Wow! Didn't she die like five years ago?
不是  她今天刚死
No, she just died today!
明天我们会举行追悼会
Okay, umm, we're having a memorial service tomorrow.
好吧  我早就参加过她的追悼会了
Okay, I know that I went to that all ready.
你没有参加过
No you didn't!
那五年前是谁死了呢
Well, then who's been dead for five years?
很多人
Well, lots of people!
说吧  你到底来不来参加追悼会
Look, are you coming to memorial service or not?
不去
Umm, no.
我以为她早死了
See I already thought she was dead
所以我的心情很平静
so I kinda made my peace with it.
而且  明天我还要去听演唱会
Plus, I'm going to a concert tomorrow.
我想邀请你去  不过呢  我只有两张票
So... I'd invite you, but umm, I only have two tickets left.
好吧  好好享受你的演唱会
Fine. Okay, enjoy your concert.
谢谢  你也好好享受葬礼
Thanks! Enjoy your funeral.
你看起来跟你儿子好像  崔比安尼太太
Wow! You look just like your son Mrs. Tribbiani!
什么  你是说我的男用挎包吗
What? Are you referring to my man's bag?
最初我以为它只是好看  没想到还非常实用
At first, I thought it just looked good, but it's practical too.
看  里面还分了层可以放各种东西
Check it out! It's got compartments for all your stuff!
钱包  钥匙  通讯录
Your wallet! Your keys! Your address book!
还有化妆品
Your make-up!
乔伊  你怎么背着包包
Joey, what are you doing with the bag?
你明天才试镜
Your audition is not until tomorrow.
但现在是三明治时间
Yeah, but sandwich time is right now.
乔伊  要是沾到芥末就不能还了
Joey, y'know you get any mustard on that bag, you can't return it.
干嘛要还  我爱这个包包
Why would I return it? I love this bag!
好吧  那你欠我三百五十块
All right, then you owe me $350.
好的  刷维不信卡还是万事不达卡
Fine! Do you take Vasa or Mustercard?
乔伊
Joey...
放心吧  我会用演这戏的片酬付包钱的
All right relax, look I'll pay you with the money from the acting job
我一定会争取到这个角色  多谢你
I am definitely gonna get thanks to you.
什么样的角色  男性反对者吗
What's the part, Anti-man?
别听他们乱说  我觉得非常性感
Hey, don't listen to them. I think it's sexy.
你加我的性感吗
U-N-I-sexy?
你好  潘奈拉太太  谢谢你来
Well hello, Mrs. Penella! Thank you so much for coming!
这是你的3D眼镜
Well, okay look, here's your umm, 3-D glasses
彭牧师会告诉大家什么时候戴上
and Reverend Pong will tell you when to put them on.
亲爱的
Hi sweetie!
-你还好吗  -还好
- Hey, how are you holding up? - Fine.
菲比  节哀顺变
Hey Pheebs, I'm so sorry.
知道吗  我外婆有个一模一样的包包
Hey, y'know what? My Grandma had the exact same bag!
我带了花来
Here, I brought you some flowers.
谢谢
Thanks!
这样感觉有男人味多了
Pulling flowers out it makes the bag look a lot more masculine.
抱歉打扰下  追悼会在这里举行吗
Oops, I'm sorry. Excuse me. Is this the umm, the memorial?
是的  欢迎
Yeah, welcome.
这是你的3D眼镜
Umm here's your 3-D glasses.
谢谢
Oh, umm, all right.
你是怎么认识弗兰西丝的
So how did you know Francis?
事实上我已经多年没见过她了
Well I actually, I-I really, I haven't seen her for years.
不过我和她及她女儿以前关系很好
But umm, well I-I was pretty tight with-with her and her daughter.
真的吗  请问尊姓大名
Really?! What's your name?
弗兰克·布菲
Umm, Frank Buffay.
更正下
Y'know what? Strike that.
其实我叫乔
My name uh, actually is-is Joe.
乔·希尔
Uh, Joe umm, Hill.
你是弗兰克·布菲吗
You're Frank Buffay?
不是  乔·希尔
Shh! No! Joe Hill!
你刚才说
You just said...
我该走了  感谢你的到来
Y'know what, I gotta go. And thank you so much for coming.
但是
But...
我的天哪
Oh my God!
-亲爱的  怎么了  -什么事
- What?! What honey? - What happened?
-那是我爸  -我的天
- That was my dad! - Oh my God!
伙计们  你们看
Hey you guys, check it out. Check it out.
我的手好像正朝着我来
It's like it's coming right at me.
追到他了吗
Oh, did you catch him?!
他怎么说
Wh-what did he say?!
他说  "很高兴认识你  葛兰达"
He said, "Nice to meet you Glenda."
我当然不能说出真名
Well, obviously I couldn't give him my real name?
为什么呢
Why?! Why not?!
你们也看到他走得像飞了  难不成
Come on, you saw the way he ran out of here! What do you think?
他会留下来跟他抛弃的女儿聊天吗
He's gonna stick around and talk to the daughter he abandoned!
那你怎么说
What did you say to him?
我自称是弗兰西丝的遗嘱执行人
Well, I said, I told him y'know, that I was the executor person
有事找他谈
of Francis' will and that I needed to talk to him
我们待会约在咖啡馆见
so I'm gonna meet him at the coffee house later.
请各位就座
Could everyone please take their seats?
我现在没办法想这个
All right, well, I just can't think about that right now.
-我只想跟我外婆告别  -好的
- I just wanna say good-bye to my Grandma. - Okay.
我们一起去吧
All right, let's go say good-bye.
我要去试镜了  我怎么样
Hey! I'm off to my audition. How do I look?
帅呆了  那个包包会让你中选的
I think you look great! Joey, that bag is gonna get you that part.
还能钓到男人
And a date with a man!
随你怎么取笑我  这个包包很棒
Y'know what? Make fun all you want. This is a great bag!
而且是好看又好用
Okay? And it's as handy as it is becoming.
你们不懂
Now, just because you don't understand something,
不代表是错的
doesn't make it wrong.
以后你们都得习惯
All right? So from now on you guys are gonna
有乔伊  就有包包
have to get used to the fact that Joey, comes with a bag!
我也该走了  我得去见我爸了
All right, I'd better go too. I got to go meet my dad.
菲比  你打算怎么说
Ooh, Pheebs, what are you gonna say?
你会表明你的身份吗
Are you gonna tell him who you are?
不会一见面就说  我不想吓跑他
Umm, no, not at first 'cause I-I don't want to freak him out.
但是你不生他气吗
Well, but aren't you pissed at him?!
这家伙遗弃了你
I mean this guy abandoned you!
如果是我
I gotta tell you if this were me,
他就等着挨揍吧
this guy would be in some serious physical danger!
我会走进去说
I mean I-I-I'd walk in there and I'd be like,
"喂  老爸
"Yo, dad!
我们现在就出去单挑"
You and me outside right now!"
我都吓到自己了
I kinda scared myself.
那起码有吓到人
Well, at least you scared someone.
真有意思  我应该很生气
Y'know it's funny, you'd think I'd be angry.
我应该很想把他的头拧下来
I mean, you'd think I'd wanna rip his tiny little head off.
幸好我已经释怀了
Fortunately, I'm past it.
菲比  你看起来有点紧张
Phoebe, you do seem a little tense.
我帮你放松下
Here, let me help you.
好的
All right.
放开我  住手
Oh! Get off!! Ow!! Oh, stop it!!
你为什么这样折磨我
Why?! Why are you doing that to me?!
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
身为一个按摩师和一个人类
As a masseuse and a human,
我恳求你永远别再帮别人按摩
I'm begging you, never do that to anyone!
我很会按摩啊
I give good massages!
在瑞秋过敏前  我一直帮她按摩的
I used to give them to Rachel all the time before she got allergic!
钱德勒也很喜欢  你看
And-and-and Chandler loves them! Watch!
他才不喜欢  他痛得快要死了
He-he does not like it! He hates it! He's in pain!
他才没有
No he's not!
他有
Yes, he is!
什么
What?!
对不起  但是  痛痛痛
I'm sorry but, ow-owww-owww!
你一直在骗我吗  我真不敢相信
You've been lying to me? I can't believe you'd do that.
也许他只是不希望你难过
Well, maybe he just didn't want to hurt your feelings.
但我们一旦开始欺骗对方
But the minute we start to lie to each other...
我说的"我们"  指的是社会
And by 'we' I mean society.
你准备好了就开始  乔伊
Any time you're ready, Joey.
你一定是新来的
Well, you must be new here.
我们找张桌子坐下  我请你喝一杯
Why don't we get a table and I'll buy you a drink.
打扰下  你能不能不要背皮包
I'm sorry. Could you, could you try it without the purse?
当然可以
Yeah, sure.
你一定是新来的
Well, you must be new here.
我们不如...
Maybe we should-
抱歉  我可以问件事吗
I'm sorry, can I ask you something?
可以  什么事
Sure. What?
第一  这不是皮包
Well, first it's not a purse.
好  再来
Okay, anytime.
别以为这是女用皮包
I mean if-if you're thinking it's a woman's bag,
不是的  这是男用包
it's not. It's a man's bag!
好的  继续吧
Okayyyy! Anddd, go!
我拿购物目录给你看
All right look, let me show you the catalog!
你看  这是最新流行  人手一个
See? Huh? It's the latest thing! Everyone's got one!
男人  女人  还有小孩都在背
Men! Women! Children! Everyone's carrying them!
你在推销这些包包吗
Umm, do you sell these bags?
不是  这些包包摆着就能卖
Noooo. No-no-no, these babies sell themselves.
谢谢  你表现得很好
Okay! Thank you! That was great!
我什么台词都还没念
Yeah but I didn't read anything.
我想这样就够了
I think we've seen enough!
那好  再见
Okay! All right, I'll see ya.
搞定了  搞定了
We got it! We got it!
-瑞秋在吗  -不在
- Hey, is Rachel here? - No.
听我说  我想为下午的事
Listen, I just wanted to apologize about this afternoon
还有按摩的事道歉  我很喜欢你的按摩
and the whole massage thing. Y'know? I-I really like 'em.
别再硬撑了
Oh, please, stop!
我们应该坦诚相对
Look, we're supposed to be honest with each other.
我只希望你能明白告诉我
I-I just wish you could tell me-just say,
"我不喜欢你的按摩"
"I don't like your massages."
我不喜欢你的按摩
I don't like your massages.
看吧  没什么
See? It's no big deal.
但是你哭了
Okay, but now see you're crying!
我不是在哭这个
I'm not crying about that!
-我是在哭工作的事  -什么事
- I'm crying about something that happened at work. - What?
我男朋友说他不喜欢我的按摩
My boyfriend said he didn't like my massages.
没关系的  你又不必事事都抢第一
It's okay, you don't have to be the best at everything.
天哪  你一点也不了解我
Oh my God! You don't know me at all!
你的按摩技术天下第一烂
Okay, you give the worst massages in the world.
我在哭耶
I'm crying here!!
听我说完
Okay, hear me out. Okay?
比烂的话你属第一
You give the best bad massages.
如果有人在找最棒的烂按摩
If anybody was looking for the best bad massage
他们自问  谁的烂技术最棒
and they were thinking to themselves, "Who's the best of that?"
那绝对非你莫属
They'd have to go to you.
你的意思是
So you're saying like umm,
如果有最佳烂按摩技术奖
if there was an award for the best bad massage,
那谁会得奖
well who would get that?
一定是你  莫妮卡
Oh, it would be you! You! Monica!
你会大获全胜
And you'd get all the votes!
或许这个奖可以叫莫妮卡奖
So maybe they could umm, call the award the Monica?
-一定会的  -好的
- Absolutely! - Okay.
我烂透了
I suck!
谢谢你来见我
Umm, thank you for meeting with me.
谢谢
Thank you. All right.
这边坐
Come, sit.
坐啊  坐
Sit. Sit!
好的  在开始之前
Umm, all righty, before we get started
你必须郑重声明
I just-I need you to state for the
你其实是弗兰克·布菲
official record that you are in fact Frank Buffay.
是的  我是
Oh yes. Yes, yes, I am, uh-hmm.
-好的  -弗兰西丝留给我什么
- Okay. - So, what did Francis leave me?
这是你找我来的原因  不是吗
Well, that's why you wanted me to come, right?
是的  的确有
Oh yes. Yes. Yeah-no. She did.
她留给你
She left you umm,
这支口红
this lipstick.
这个
It's huh, well it's
这是用过的
oh it's-ew used.
酷
Umm, cool.
我要请教几个问题
Okay. I have just a few questions to ask
我把相关表格拿出来
so I'm going to get out my official forms.
第一个问题
Okay, so, question 1.
你
You and uh,
你娶了弗兰西丝的女儿莉莉  对吗
you were married to Francis' daughter Lilly, is that correct?
对  没错
Yes, yes I was.
第二个问题
Okay, umm, question 2.
这段婚姻最终
Umm, did that marriage end
A  很美满  B  普通
A. Happily, B. Medium,
C  你抛弃了妻子
or C. In the total abandonment of her
和两个孩子
and her two children?
表上真的这么写的吗
It really says that?!
对  你看
Yeah. See?
那我就得选C了
Well then I guess then I-I would I would have to say C.
抛妻弃女
Hmm, okay, total abandonment.
抛弃的原因
Okay, reasons for abandonment,
A  极机密政府工作
A. Top secret government work,
B  失忆症
B. Amnesia,
或是C  你就是个自私
or C. You're just a selfish,
不负责的大坏蛋
irresponsible bad, bad man?
其实我没那么想要这支口红
Y'know, I don't think I want the lipstick that much.
请你帮个忙
But umm... Oh, would you do me a favor?
麻烦你
And umm, would you,
请把这个交给莉莉
would you give Lilly that, please?
什么
What?!
请你见到莉莉时  把那张纸条交给她
Well Lilly, when you see Lilly would you give her that, that note?
我本来想在追悼会上找她谈
Because I wanted to talk to her at the memorial but,
但我觉得她会冲我发飙
well I pictured her getting mad at me
就像你这样  我就临阵退缩了
the way you got mad at me and I well, I chickened out.
我写了那张纸条  请帮我转交
So, uh, I wrote her that note, would you give it to her please?
你是来找莉莉的吗
But you-you-you came to see Lilly?
对  怎么了
Yeah, yeah. Why?
莉莉死了
Lilly's dead.
什么
She what?!
她死了
She's dead.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
没死就被火化  那问题就太严重了
Well, if she isn't then cremating her was a big mistake.
我真不敢相信  我不敢相信
I can't believe this. I just-I can't believe this.
怎么会  天啊  多久的事
How-how-Oh my God. How long ago?
17年前
17 years ago.
那两个女儿呢
What about, what about the girls?
厄休拉在当服务生  住在苏豪区
Well, Ursula is a waitress and-and she lives in Soho.
菲比
And Phoebe,
就坐在这张沙发上
is on this couch.
没错  口红和女儿  你今天撞大运了
Yep, lipstick and a daughter, big day for you!
菲比  我...  哎呀
Phoebe, I-I-I-umm,  Oops.
我不知道该说什么
I just, I-I-I-I don't, I don't know what to say.
真不敢相信你居然是我的女儿
I just can't believe that you're my daughter,
你长得这么漂亮
you're so pretty.
是的  但你跑题了
Yes. Well, that's neither here nor there.
如果我说我很抱歉自己
So would it, would it make you feel better
当年离开了  你会不会好过一点
if I said I was very, very sorry that I left?
你说什么都不重要了
Y'know what, it doesn't matter what you say
事已至此  所以你可以走了
it's not gonna make a difference anyway, so you can just go.
好  我得辩解下
All right. Well, y'know in my defense
我是个不称职的父亲
I was a lousy father.
这叫辩解吗
That's a defense?
没错  我把牛奶烧焦
Yes. Yes it is. I burned the formula
把尿布包反
and I put your diapers on backwards.
我编了一首歌哄你睡觉
I mean, I made up a song to help you sleep,
结果你哭得更厉害
but that made you cry even more!
你会写歌吗
You make up songs?
是  不过只有那一首  而且很白痴
Well no, just-just that one. But, it was stupid.
我想想怎么唱的
Let's see, how did it, how did it go. Umm.
困女儿  困女儿
Sleepy girl, sleepy girl.
你为什么不睡觉呢
Why won't you go to sleep?
困女儿  困女儿
Sleepy girl, sleepy girl.
你让我也睡不成
You're, you're, you're keeping me uppp!
我只是  不懂得表达感情
I just, I y'know, I'm not very good at this. So, umm...
那我来吧
Well, I am.
我也没准备好
Not yet, no.
试镜如何
Hey man, how did the audition go?
艾丝特尔说我没戏
Estelle said I didn't get it.
什么  为什么
What?! Why?
乔伊  你再合适不过了
Joey you were so ready for it!
我也有同感
Yeah, I thought so too but,
不过她说选角的人对我有看法
she said the casting people had some problems with me.
什么看法
What kind of problem?
说老实话
Well to tell you the truth, they uh,
-他们看不惯我的包  -我的天
- they had a problem with the bag! - My god!
反正也是出烂戏
Y'know what? It was a stupid play anyway!
乔伊  我想是时候和这个包说再见了
Y'know, Joey, I think it's time to give up the bag.
我可不想和它分开
I don't wanna give up the bag.
我可以留着它对吗  瑞秋
I don't have to give up the bag! Do I Rach?
你也认为我应该放弃它
Oh, you think I should give up the bag!
乔伊  对不起
Honey wait, Joey, I'm sorry
我觉得你背起来很帅
I mean as terrific as I think you are with it...
但世人或许还没办法接受
...I just don't know if the world is ready
你和你的包包
for you and your bag.
你居然这么说
I can't believe I'm hearing this!
等等  等等
Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
我不是说你不该带包包
I'm not saying that you shouldn't have a bag,
我是说你可以用
I just-it's just there are other bags
其它争议性比较小的包包
you know that maybe a little less umm, controversial.
对  叫做男式皮夹
Yeah umm, they're called wallets.